[Music]
you're watching yoga with AJ where I'll
be teaching you Surya namaskar so let's
get started stretch your hands up and
come first to namaskar mudra stretch
your arms up gently Arch back as you
exhale we're going to reach forward and
down and if you need to bend your knees
to get your palms down onto the mat if
you can't get your palms down on the
floor maybe you have just your
fingertips down on the floor Now we move
to ashas sanchalan the equestrian pose
step your right leg back as much as you
can and rest the right knee down on the
floor stretch the toes out behind you
press the fingertips or the Palms down
and look
up gently press the Palms down curl the
right toe under pick up the right knee
your body is in a nice straight line
you're going to move into that plank or
push-up like position by sliding the
left leg
back now gently bring the knees
down bring your chest down between your
hands keeping the hips up and the elbows
tucked into the body and rest your chin
down on the
mat inhale and gently slide forward
elbows are tucked
in bent you're going to try and look up
if you can stretch your toes out on the
mat behind you press the Palms down into
the floor and going straight up into the
inverted whe coming back to the
equestrian pose from this inverted V
just swing your leg forward between your
hands and then gently place your left
knee down onto the mat look up can try
and have your palms down if they allow
you gently curl your left toes under
pick up the left knee take a giant step
forward with your left leg now you can
either have your knees bent here
fingertips just touching the floor or if
your legs allow you you can straighten
up the legs and press the Palms down
gently draw the head into the knees from
here we're going to reach forward trying
to come to a tabletop position reaching
to the other end of the room gently
coming up arching back softly and
bringing the arms down thank you for
spending your time and your energy with
me you're watching yoga with
AJ